<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spacehustler on Gustav Jansson</title>
    <link>https://madeso.github.io/tags/spacehustler/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spacehustler on Gustav Jansson</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 13:53:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://madeso.github.io/tags/spacehustler/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The road that follows</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-roadthatfollows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 13:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-roadthatfollows/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I really want to release a demo to get a feedback on the actual game, but there are a few things that I think should be fixed before I release a early preview build:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Redesign the hardcoded input system, I’m working on this now&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add lights and shadows to the renderer, this will really help the player determine the depth when flying around and help immersion&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add 2d rendering/menu, this will provide the GUI for the “press start to play” so the game know what control to accept input from&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Physics motor, this is perhaps the most important feature. This will allow the player to control the heading of the ship while the motor control the amount of torque to apply to keep that heading&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;First person/cockpit view, as I pretty much already have oculus rift support, this is a given, however given the way the craft moves it might make you really dizzy.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development stories</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-devstories/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2013 13:52:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-devstories/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s been a while since I posted, but I have been buried deep in rift and input&#xA;development. Rift development is pretty much done and I have rift support. I&#xA;have received my &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Razer_Hydra&#34;&gt;razer hydra&lt;/a&gt; and backed the stem system and I’m hoping I’ll&#xA;receive my &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/89577853/stem-system-the-best-way-to-interact-with-virtual&#34;&gt;sixense stem&lt;/a&gt; system in July.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oculus development</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-oculus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2013 13:48:53 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-oculus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m in the middle of adding oculus rift support to my engine, this is what happens when you mix up your matrices:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;matrix.png&#34; alt=&#34;matrix fail&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ship designs</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-shipdesigns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 13:45:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-shipdesigns/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bought myself a stylus and installed &lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.adsk.sketchbookhdexpress&amp;amp;hl=en&#34;&gt;sketchbook express&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;on my nexus 7 and sketched some lander ships, this is the result:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;s1.png&#34; alt=&#34;sketch 1&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;s2.png&#34; alt=&#34;sketch 2&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;s3.png&#34; alt=&#34;sketch 3&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;s4.png&#34; alt=&#34;sketch 4&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on the controls</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 13:42:58 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-controls/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have started implementing the basic controls for both the keyboard and joysticks&#xA;and to test everything out I added basic thrust and torque controls, and while this&#xA;is really hard to control as each torque requires a counter torque from stopping&#xA;to spinning I started thinking. The &lt;a href=&#34;http://lanael.free.fr/webgl/hopper.html&#34;&gt;WebGL version of lander&lt;/a&gt; and I recall the original&#xA;(I still can’t get it to play on my win7 system) let’s you enter the desired orientation&#xA;and let a AI controls the torque thrusts. This is a much easier control scheme as you don’t&#xA;have to compensate for the rotational adjustments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working hard</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-workinghard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 13:40:53 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-workinghard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m working hard, soon I will have input partly completed but in the meantime have a look at the physics in action on these stand-in graphics:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;fall.gif&#34; alt=&#34;ship falling&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The music</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2013 13:28:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-music/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Development on the game engine has been slow this past week so this week I’ve been thinking about the background music for the game. I don’t know the actual graphical style of the game just yet but I think I narrowed down the musical style to either some slow form of swing/jazz like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/8jzlJeKZ4w0?autoplay=0&amp;controls=1&amp;end=0&amp;loop=0&amp;mute=0&amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&#xA;      &gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or some some ambient &lt;a href=&#34;http://opengameart.org/content/through-space&#34;&gt;80’s style electro music like this&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Distribution</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-distribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 13:36:13 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-distribution/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week instead of talking just design I thought I would be nice to share some development ideas that I’ve been brewing for a while, and it has to do with distribution of the game. The obvious choice is steam, and probably the equivalent to the appstore on ubuntu(if that still exists and is flourishing), but a part of me wants to sell the game to all linux distributions and I can’t test that at all.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Name of the game</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 13:34:01 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-name/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I though this is good time to talk and clarify a little about the game and blog title, and how misleading that title might be.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First and foremost the game is not set in space. The game might take place on different planets and you might travel from these places, but this is not part of the game.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Neither is hustling of any kind. You are a soldier/mercenary/technician for hire, you do your job and you get paid, so no hustling whatsoever.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A modern cockpit view</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-cockpit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 13:31:22 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-cockpit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;cockpit.png&#34; alt=&#34;A illustration of a ww2 cockpit&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I never really liked the cockpit view of flying and driving games. It provies a sense of realism for sure, but I never believed it provided me with a view that I liked. Enter E3 2012 and the demonstration of the Oculus Rift. Together with a helicopter like transparent sphere like cockpit the cockpit view field of view that the rift provides and the slow speed of the craft it provide a sense of realism few games can match.&#xA;the oculus rift&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on mission types</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-missiontypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2013 13:25:01 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-missiontypes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I’ve been thinking a lot about the different skirmish and mission types. The original lander basically had fetch an object and destroy missions. Hopper introduced “challenges” in the form of land without taking any damage and races, and while this could be expanded upon with acrobatical challenges(move through a narrow gap) and survival challenges (survive a meteor rain) I want to expand further in the mission and challenge/skirmish varieties.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on the artstyle</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-artstyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2013 13:20:12 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-artstyle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since I started working on Space Hustler I’ve been thinking about what art style the game should have. The original lander had a sci-fi style and while that will work there are a lot of sci fi games and sci fi shooters especially are a dime a dozen. Partly because of this I’ve been thinking about designin a little bit different.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One idea I’ve been tossing around is the World War 2 with jet engines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flowstorm</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-flowstorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 13:18:10 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-flowstorm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/BOI35480vdo?autoplay=0&amp;controls=1&amp;end=0&amp;loop=0&amp;mute=0&amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&#xA;      &gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I attended the &lt;a href=&#34;http://nordicgame.com/?id=73&#34;&gt;nordic game indie night&lt;/a&gt;, and got to play &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.flowstormgame.com/&#34;&gt;flowstorm&lt;/a&gt; (that did&#xA;a &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/740665854/flowstorm&#34;&gt;kickstarter&lt;/a&gt;) and&#xA;realized 2 things: It’t a really hard game and that it’s also a lander-like 2d game.&#xA;Check it out if you haven’t already.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>And so it begins...</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-begins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 13:15:57 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-begins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So I decided that I need to make a bigger game, a game that I can work on for a&#xA;few months at least and not get bored. I shouldn’t have any complicated animations&#xA;and should be “easy” to make. A basic renderer on the top of a physics simulation&#xA;won’t be that complicated and could be fun.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I thought about remaking a previous game of mine, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BjG1_d7Fxc8&amp;amp;feature=player_detailpage#t=13s&#34;&gt;lolball&lt;/a&gt;, but all the design I&#xA;could come up with was way to complicated for what I had imagined. All hope seemed&#xA;to be lost and my motivation for creating something was low.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
