<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>home on Gustav Jansson</title>
    <link>https://madeso.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in home on Gustav Jansson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 07:37:38 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://madeso.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Week29</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 22:38:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week29/</guid>
      <description>This week I didnt do much, and I&amp;rsquo;m honestly not sure what I did except work related stuff, shopping a few new furnitures and attending a birthday party. Work on the graph widget has been lacking theese last weeks and I desperetly both want and need it to be finished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restarting Alsa</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/restart-alsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 14:31:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/restart-alsa/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes after I wake up my computer after a hibernate I notice that sound is not playing. A simple fix for this seems to be to restart alsa:
$ pulseaudio -k &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo alsa force-reload  Found on Stack overflow</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week28</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 22:52:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week28/</guid>
      <description>This week I mostly watched season 4 of &amp;ldquo;Agents of Shield&amp;rdquo;, but I also added proper smiley graphics and pagination and fixed a bug causing the image on some pages to not be displayed so at least I made some progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week27</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week27/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 08:24:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week27/</guid>
      <description>This week I continued working on the graph widget. I also found 2 earlier blogs of mine and moved all of them here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week26</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 07:33:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week26/</guid>
      <description>This week I pretty much continued on NodeCalc and the graph widget driving it all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week25</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 21:07:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week25/</guid>
      <description>This week I started on a project called nodecalc. It aims to replace my need for most excel/open office calc needs by calculating expressions in a graph like manner instead of referencing cells.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week24</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week24/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 07:16:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week24/</guid>
      <description>This week I spent time learning various unity things, trying to up my unity game. I also started learning blender and trying (and failing) to make a 3d character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week23</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 08:43:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week23/</guid>
      <description>This week I entered the no more sweden gamejam and made a game called &amp;ldquo;Looking for love&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week22</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 21:22:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week22/</guid>
      <description>This week started with a small project of creating a tracery.io commandline application in C++. It currently missing some advanced features but it was a nice break in the great konmari cleansing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week21</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 07:19:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week21/</guid>
      <description>This was a little bit better. I watched a little bit of netflix, but converted the current deploy script from bash to python so I, in the future, can add more advanced image rezising functions that hugo currently doesnt support. Then I pretty much started the konmari appartment cleanup so I guess I wont get much development stuff done for a couple of weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week20</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 21:07:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week20/</guid>
      <description>This week was also lazy. What can I say, except I&amp;rsquo;ve now binged one more series on netflix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A fix for spotify filling up the C: drive</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/spotify-windows-ssd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 07:28:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/spotify-windows-ssd/</guid>
      <description>I recently got a notice that my SSD C: drive was getting low on space and after a quick check with WinDirStat I noticed that spoitfy was filling it up with loads of weird files in the AppData\Local\Spotify\Data folder, even after I have moved my cache location.
It turns out the &amp;ldquo;cached location&amp;rdquo; is only the saved playlists, and the Data folder is the cached songs that arent in a playlist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week19</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 08:42:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week19/</guid>
      <description>This week should have been spent on either gaf, t3d or finishing the spacetyper menu but it was spent on finishing crappy series on netflix instead. I guess the blame is mostly on the bad cycle of beeing too tired and then just binge watching myself one more episode past bedtime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week18</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 21:07:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week18/</guid>
      <description>This week I continued working on this homepage, scaling images to fit in the design and it&amp;rsquo;s taking longer than expected. I also finally restarted my tile based 3d level editor called t3d. Since it&amp;rsquo;s still in its infancy there arent any pretty pictures so I&amp;rsquo;ll keep it here in the devlog for now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week17</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 20:46:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week17/</guid>
      <description>Much of the page is now in &amp;ldquo;kinda working&amp;rdquo; order. There are still projects missing images and download links, and most projects have the wrong header image size. There only one thing to do, and that&amp;rsquo;s keep on working on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week16</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 00:12:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week16/</guid>
      <description>This week I did a little work on gaf, but my whole weeked was spent on moving my blogs and page to this new hugo based page. It isn&amp;rsquo;t done yet, but hopefully soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:15:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello I am Gustav.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week15</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 19:54:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week15/</guid>
      <description>This week I continued working on gaf, now supporting json loading and default values, next up is array support (yay)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week14</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 15:16:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week14/</guid>
      <description>I continued working on gaf, and currently it parses a few test files, generate some c++11 code and runs a few unit tests on Travis. Next up is adding Json io and enums or arrays</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week13</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 23:41:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week13/</guid>
      <description>Last week was kinda productive despite a birthday party in Germany. I finally started on gaf, the game format file format generator, and separated the game and the engine part of spacetyper into super and sub repos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week12</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 23:23:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week12/</guid>
      <description>Last week wasn&amp;rsquo;t that eventful. Life got in my way I guess so no code was neither written nor committed. Better luck next(this) week I guess&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week11</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 07:07:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week11/</guid>
      <description>I did nothing at all this week except watching Netflix. I managed to watch the entire Jessica Jones season 1 though so I&amp;rsquo;m both proud and appalled about my accomplishment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week10</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 00:21:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week10/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t really been doing that much last week. Instead of staring designing or coding the 2d rendering system I started on separating the engine repo from the game repo, but nothing is complete yet. I hope I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to finish it this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week9</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 05:44:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week9/</guid>
      <description>This week I didn&amp;rsquo;t do much, except implementing radix sort with count sort as the second sorter. Pretty standard I guess but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t in my toolbox library and I will need it for the upcoming render optimization</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week8</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 12:25:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/devlog/week8/</guid>
      <description>This week I replaced the built-in assert with a custom one to get callstack information, and I&amp;rsquo;ve also finally completed the rewrite of the new opengl buffer rendering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoelacing</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/shoelacing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 14:39:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/shoelacing/</guid>
      <description>I recently bought new shoes and needed to lace them, hence it&amp;rsquo;s time to google how to lace shoes again. Ians shoelace site is my favorite and I&amp;rsquo;ve been visiting it for what it seems like an eternity. I don&amp;rsquo;t know much about the competition, but I can&amp;rsquo;t find anything missing from it. It&amp;rsquo;s the best!
http://www.fieggen.com/shoelace/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep your ubuntu-gnome from waking up at random</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/gnomewakeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 14:34:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/gnomewakeup/</guid>
      <description>I have tried using /proc/acpi/wakeup and I&amp;rsquo;ve tried looking in /sys/bus/usb/devices/SOMETHING/power/wakeup for devices that will wake up the computer, however I finally fixed my random wakeup problems with a tool called acpitool.
It is really quite simple. First you need to install it, unless you already have it installed:
$ sudo apt-get install acpitool  Once it&amp;rsquo;s installed you can list what you can do with it, and to make it works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non recursive file searching in Nautilus</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/nonerecursivesearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 13:07:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/nonerecursivesearch/</guid>
      <description>Recursive search is the default in nautilus (search in subfolders), but I prefer type ahead search(only search in current folder).
This is easy to change, but not very obvious. In dconf-editor navigate to org &amp;gt; gnome &amp;gt; nautilus &amp;gt; preferences and set the enable-interactive-search value to what you&amp;rsquo;d like to use.
http://www.webupd8.org/2014/01/nautilus-type-ahead-find-feature.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revert google&#43; to a standard blogger profile on blogger</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/googleplusblogger/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 19:29:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/googleplusblogger/</guid>
      <description>It turns out google has removed it from various links, so I don&amp;rsquo;t know how long this link will last, but here it goes:
http://www.blogger.com/revert-profile.g﻿
Pretty simple but it took far too long to find it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Folders before files in ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/foldersbeforefiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 19:13:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/foldersbeforefiles/</guid>
      <description>I like to view folders before my files with Files/Nautilus, and here is how to enable it:
In dconf-editor navigate to: org.gnome.nautilus.preferences key and set sort-directories-first to true.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 wakes up from sleep at random</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/win10wakeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 19:12:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/win10wakeup/</guid>
      <description>After upgrading to Windows 10, my computer started randomly waking up. This extensive guide on superuser has proven time and time again to be a perfect guide to keep windows from waking up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test markdown</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/test/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a code chunk with syntax highlighting:
var foo = function(x) { return(x + 5); } foo(3)  $ echo $EDITOR vim $ git checkout master Switched to branch &#39;master&#39; Your branch is up-to-date with &#39;origin/master&#39;. $ git push Everything up-to-date $ echo &#39;All &amp;gt; done!&#39; All done!  You can write regular markdown here and Jekyll will automatically convert it to a nice webpage. I strongly encourage you to take 5 minutes to learn how to write in markdown - it&amp;rsquo;ll teach you how to transform regular text into bold/italics/headings/tables/etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The road that follows</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-roadthatfollows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 13:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-roadthatfollows/</guid>
      <description>I really want to release a demo to get a feedback on the actual game, but there are a few things that I think should be fixed before I release a early preview build:
 Redesign the hardcoded input system, I’m working on this now Add lights and shadows to the renderer, this will really help the player determine the depth when flying around and help immersion Add 2d rendering/menu, this will provide the GUI for the “press start to play” so the game know what control to accept input from Physics motor, this is perhaps the most important feature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development stories</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-devstories/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2013 13:52:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-devstories/</guid>
      <description>It’s been a while since I posted, but I have been buried deep in rift and input development. Rift development is pretty much done and I have rift support. I have received my razer hydra and backed the stem system and I’m hoping I’ll receive my sixense stem system in July.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on the controls</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 13:42:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-controls/</guid>
      <description>I have started implementing the basic controls for both the keyboard and joysticks and to test everything out I added basic thrust and torque controls, and while this is really hard to control as each torque requires a counter torque from stopping to spinning I started thinking. The WebGL version of lander and I recall the original (I still can’t get it to play on my win7 system) let’s you enter the desired orientation and let a AI controls the torque thrusts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The music</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2013 13:28:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-music/</guid>
      <description>Development on the game engine has been slow this past week so this week I’ve been thinking about the background music for the game. I don’t know the actual graphical style of the game just yet but I think I narrowed down the musical style to either some slow form of swing/jazz like this:
  Or some some ambient 80’s style electro music like this.
Given the I’ve already found some electro music that seems to be fitting and that lander used some similar music pieces, it’s safe to assume that I will be using that electro music during the early alpha builds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Distribution</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-distribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 13:36:13 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-distribution/</guid>
      <description>This week instead of talking just design I thought I would be nice to share some development ideas that I’ve been brewing for a while, and it has to do with distribution of the game. The obvious choice is steam, and probably the equivalent to the appstore on ubuntu(if that still exists and is flourishing), but a part of me wants to sell the game to all linux distributions and I can’t test that at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Name of the game</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 13:34:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-name/</guid>
      <description>I though this is good time to talk and clarify a little about the game and blog title, and how misleading that title might be.
First and foremost the game is not set in space. The game might take place on different planets and you might travel from these places, but this is not part of the game.
Neither is hustling of any kind. You are a soldier/mercenary/technician for hire, you do your job and you get paid, so no hustling whatsoever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flowstorm</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-flowstorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 13:18:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-flowstorm/</guid>
      <description>I attended the nordic game indie night, and got to play flowstorm (that did a kickstarter) and realized 2 things: It’t a really hard game and that it’s also a lander-like 2d game. Check it out if you haven’t already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And so it begins...</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-begins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 13:15:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/sh-begins/</guid>
      <description>So I decided that I need to make a bigger game, a game that I can work on for a few months at least and not get bored. I shouldn’t have any complicated animations and should be “easy” to make. A basic renderer on the top of a physics simulation won’t be that complicated and could be fun.
I thought about remaking a previous game of mine, lolball, but all the design I could come up with was way to complicated for what I had imagined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m not dead</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-notdead/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 12:19:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-notdead/</guid>
      <description>Whoa… almost 5 months since last time! I gotta post more than twice a year 🙂
Anyways, I’ve been quite busy since last time:
 My pwn game library is still in development. and I’ve entered ludum dare twice..  I’ve posted my first entry, let’s go cave exploring, earlier in this blog. My second entry for the “Explore” theme was “Xplorer – the game” a kinda unfinished 2-player game that ends when everything is explored</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve been busy</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-busy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2009 12:16:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-busy/</guid>
      <description>Since last time I’ve entered Ludum Dare and actually finished at 75ths place and a bronze in community – yay me.
Since then I’ve integrated the half/16-bit float from the glorious OpenEXR-project into my game-library pwn.
I’ve also been thinking about creating a 2d level editor as editing text-files suck, and there doesn’t seem to be a good level-editor. Most of the 2d level editors are focused on tile-based editing, but I want a more free-flow sprite-based editor, like the aquaria editor(nicely captured by wolfire design tour) or the boingo editor that is briefly visible in their sga trailer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh, the temptation</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-temptation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 12:12:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-temptation/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epic fail</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-epicfail/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 11:26:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-epicfail/</guid>
      <description>I probably should have posted this earlier, however I been sleeping and sobbing over the fact that I didn’t finish no more sweden :). A few hours before deadline all tiles in one layer went 3 tiles up, but collision-tiles were still in the same place. I though that was strange so I went to check the map in the (external) editor, and to my horror it didn’t load. No message, no crash nor any exception – just silence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No more sweden - It can&#39;t be true</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-nomoresweden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 11:20:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-nomoresweden/</guid>
      <description>So I’m attending this game-jam called No more sweden(funny name) this week. Wednesday/Thursday to Saturday/Sunday. I’ll be attending most of it, though I have to work at Thursday and Friday, which is a bummer, so Ive been thinking at what kind of game I’m be making. I’ve been thinking about making a simple plat former for some time now, and this might be good time as any to make it a reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yo frankie!</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-yofrankie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 11:18:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-yofrankie/</guid>
      <description>Given that I sacked tetris more than a month ago, gamedev has been pretty stale at the moment. I’ve been studying fighting-systems and analysing combo-lists for the fighting-system in survivors. The usual stuff. However since the last post I’ve been thinking about remaking Yo Frankie! with my tetris engine.
Tetris actually outlived it’s purpose, as the purpose of the tetris project was to build a solid foundation for survivors and all my other 3d games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excursions into the UI</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-ui-excursions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2009 11:08:13 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-ui-excursions/</guid>
      <description>I recently read scarabus’ post regarding guis and I wanted to follow up/ add a few notes of my own. Since scarabus considers blender to have the worst user-interface(ui for short), I’m going to compare it to other similar applications and guess why it might be non-intuitive.
So, beeing picky I have tried several mesh modelers. The imcomplete list is anim8or, google sketchup, misfit model 3d, xsi modtool, blender, art of illusion, truespace and wings 3d.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tetris got sacked!</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-tetris-sacked/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2009 11:06:13 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-tetris-sacked/</guid>
      <description>I recently came to the conclusion that I wont continue tetris, and instead restart my third person shooter-beatemup zombie &amp;amp; soldier slayfest Survivors. I always knew I was going back to survivors, I just didn’t know that I was going to give up on tetris. In reality it has to do with I got bored and can’t come up with a satisfying way of designing the menys. It sucks really, but all of the time wont go to waste since most of the code is basic boilerplate and I’m happy with most of the layout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re doomed (not)</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-darkangel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2009 11:02:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-darkangel/</guid>
      <description>Apparently the pulse didnt came. Now my biggest problem apperently is if I’m such a great nerd because I noticed or I blogged about it.
 On June 1, 2009, months after Max’s escape, terrorists detonate an electromagnetic pulse weapon in the atmosphere over the U.S., which destroys the vast majority of computer and communication systems, throwing the country into utter chaos.
 Source: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dark_Angel_(TV_series)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stairway to heaven</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-stairway/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 11:01:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-stairway/</guid>
      <description>I recently discovered, not only do the local library have CD’s full of modern music, with my chemical romance-blood among others(despite what you think of chemical romance, blood really is different), they also have a complete collection of sound fx CD’s. I guess I dont have to spend some of my hard earned money on thoose sorts of CD’s when I can borrow 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foobar sorting</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-foobar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2009 10:55:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-foobar/</guid>
      <description>Since some time I’ve been sorting my music collection. Going though my hard-drives and Cd’s finding all music-files and moving them to a common place and with the help of foobar2000 place them in a sane directory-structure and keep them there.
Within foobar I sort the artists on the following script. This makes sure that The (International) Noise Conspiracy is among the other artist that begins with I.
$replace($replace($replace($stripprefix(%artist%),’|’,),&#39;[‘,),&#39;(‘,)  That little script keeps things nice and tidy within foobar, but to sort I use these two massive scripts:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is there a bone in your shell?</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-shellbone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2009 10:54:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-shellbone/</guid>
      <description>I managed to get my skeleton loader working and I had some problem roatating the turtle 360 degrees but when I enabled ShortSlerp and fixed a few bugs in the angle-loading routine it worked as expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operating system not found</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-osnotfound/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 10:47:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-osnotfound/</guid>
      <description>I had a nightmare a few nights ago. In the dream I apparently had formated my computer without doing a backup of my important data. Luckily it was only a dream…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, I am Gustav</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 10:40:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-hello/</guid>
      <description>.. and I’m a game programmer. My best game so far would probably be lolball. A game where you move through levels as fast as possible to get a better score, all while doing as many combos as possible. Did I mention particle effects and slow-motion? Currently however I’m working on a remake of tetris so I can get a stable codebase for my next progress.
Until next time…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 10:38:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/wp-firstpost/</guid>
      <description>As the current year is slowly coming to a close, I figured that it would be smart to make a few promises. The first would be to actually add a new post once in a while, say every week, instead of once a year. So who am I…? Stay tuned for my next update 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>