<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gustav Janssons devlog </title>
    <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/</link>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;This blog is a try to me keep motivates and a way to see my progress on my current projects. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how it goes!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 23:40:32 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/devlog/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    
    
    

    
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 12</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 22:56:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-12/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week, due to covid-19, I worked from home. I implemented the drunken bishop algorithm and continued working on the argparse module. Hopefully I will get done with the argparse soon so I get get back to working on the cellular automata, sprator and my scripting language.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 11</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 20:14:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-11/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I worked on new argparse module, some cellular automata/procedural content generation and another identicon image generator.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 10</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 22:45:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I restructured the cmakes for euphoria, and finished the refactoring of the arch install commands, then I got stuck in netflix land and watched both  witcher and season 2 of altered carbon. Hopefully net week the netflix craze has left me again so I can get back to being productive :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 09</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 20:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-09/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I continued on the raytracer, spent time on my arch install scripts since I&amp;rsquo;m preparing on installing arch on a new computer, but most of the weekend was spent on watching netflix since I just managed to update chrome on my main machine.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 08</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 22:35:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-08/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I continued on the raytracer. It&amp;rsquo;s going slower than I want, but there is progress atleast :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 07</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 19:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-07/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I started work on the &amp;ldquo;Raytracer in a weekend&amp;rdquo; project in preperation for playing with Open MP and a upcomming CUDA talk I&amp;rsquo;m attending.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 06</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 21:19:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-06/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I bought a windows laptop that I can use for gamejams and to help me better support windows as a platform for my games.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 05</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 22:42:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-05/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I spent mostly on arch installations, switching from my custom script to getting confortable with yay and trying to recover more computers that I can install arch on, but so far no luck. The weekend was spent on creating a entry for global game jam, and I expect it will appear under projects here soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 04</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 20:01:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-04/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most of my time this week have been spent either on reading or watching things. I really should just sit down and program for 5 minutes instead of watching random youtube clips. Next weeking is the global game jam, so I will atleast do some game things then :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 03</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 21:16:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There weren&amp;rsquo;t lot of dev time this week either. I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking at the bytecode and a basic assembler and disassembler for it. I&amp;rsquo;ve also commited a few rouge files found in the euphoria repo, but nothing major.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 02</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 22:00:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-02/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I been mostly handling real-world stuff and only manage to a little bit of work on euphoria, mainly fixing the travis build. Better luck next week I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 23:04:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First week of the new year. I started replacing my cutom log with spdlog and updating paths from strings to a dir/file path struct and continued the work on parsing the synty assets that I bought during black friday. There is still some work before euphoria can load and render it correctly but it&amp;rsquo;s coming along&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 52</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-52/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 22:19:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-52/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the last devlog of the year and unfortunatley I haven&amp;rsquo;t done much on either euphoria or fel this week as I&amp;rsquo;ve spended most of it with friends and family. However I started replacing the custom log with spdlog so that is atleast something&amp;hellip; :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 51</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-51/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 21:45:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-51/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I added grid snapping, simple object movement and selection to t3d.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 50</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 22:24:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-50/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I continued the work on t3d and can now place items on a grid. Hopefully next week I can get back to working on fel for a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
