<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gustav Janssons devlog </title>
    <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/</link>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;This blog is a try to me keep motivates and a way to see my progress on my current projects. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how it goes!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 23:40:32 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/devlog/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    
    
    

    
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 34</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 23:39:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-34/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I started working again. I did a little work on my software synth and my dotfiles management util/script. In less than a week is the gmtk gamejam and I&amp;rsquo;m getting hyped.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 33</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 23:04:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-33/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I started on software synth, and participated in game jam but didn&amp;rsquo;t
really finish it :( On the upside is I added a feature to the assimp library
and terminal application that I soon hopefully will add via a pull request.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 32</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 00:40:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-32/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I mostly spend relaxing and real life stuff. I made a few small games in godot and started on switching my main system from ubuntu to arch.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 31</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 20:52:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-31/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week was my first vacation and I added a OnInit function and creation arguments
to the the create function in euphoria. I also, in preperation of the upcomming gamejams,
started to play around with godot a bit and started on a smaller platformer test/game thing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 30</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 22:20:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-30/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week a heatwave struck, so I didn&amp;rsquo;t really do much. I started on the
OnInit callback, but that&amp;rsquo;s pretty much it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 29</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 22:34:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-29/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I made it so that shots are destroyed when the have left the viewport.
I also started laying the grounds for adding a init function for when creating entities.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 28</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 22:49:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I merged the main.cc from all various applications in the euphoria
framework, extracting all the copy-paste code into another utility file.
I also finally came up with how to best handle how to check for when objects
are outside the viewport, so that should be done soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 27</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 22:23:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-27/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I finished the viewport logic, and started looking at how to handle objects getting outside of the view. Not uch but I also binged luke cage season 2, so pretty ok progress considering.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 26</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 23:13:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-26/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I spent on watching luke cage season 2, adding enum support to imgui
option for gaf, fixed the issue with not resusing ids and started on writing
viewport handling. The latter is not quite finished yet, but it&amp;rsquo;s getting there.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 25</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 23:49:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week consisted mostly of real life stuff, but I managed to fix a few gaf related things. Next week should hopefulle be more productive.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 24</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 23:04:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I continued work on the editor and gaf and it&amp;rsquo;s finally getting near completion.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 23</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 17:43:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I threw out the wx scimed/ninepatch editor and have now a improved
dear imgui version of it. There still are some non imgui like parts from the ported
code but things are looking better. I just started on the imgui extension for gaf,
and after that is completed I can work on saving json so I can close this chapter.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 22</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 21:47:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I mostly finished the move from protobuf to gaf. I still can&amp;rsquo;t save
gaf files, but that will come after I throw out the current wxWidgets based
editor, and that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;m working on now.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 21</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 23:45:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I contintued the work on my protobuf replacement library, gaf, and
actually started on replacing protobuf in euphoria. I hope that by the time of
the next devlog I have finished the refactoring.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 20</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 01:14:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2018-20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I basically just went through the entire list of errors that clang-tidy
can detect and decided what to use, and what to ignore, and fixed several warnings.
Then I continued workin on my protobuf replacement library, gaf, that I started ages ago.
Hopefully within a week or two I can replace protobuf in euphoria soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
