<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gustav Janssons devlog </title>
    <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/</link>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;This blog is a try to me keep motivates and a way to see my progress on my current projects. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how it goes!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 23:40:32 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/devlog/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    
    
    

    
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 08</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 22:35:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-08/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I continued on the raytracer. It&amp;rsquo;s going slower than I want, but there is progress atleast :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 07</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 19:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-07/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I started work on the &amp;ldquo;Raytracer in a weekend&amp;rdquo; project in preperation for playing with Open MP and a upcomming CUDA talk I&amp;rsquo;m attending.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 06</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 21:19:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-06/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I bought a windows laptop that I can use for gamejams and to help me better support windows as a platform for my games.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 05</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 22:42:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-05/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I spent mostly on arch installations, switching from my custom script to getting confortable with yay and trying to recover more computers that I can install arch on, but so far no luck. The weekend was spent on creating a entry for global game jam, and I expect it will appear under projects here soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 04</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 20:01:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-04/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most of my time this week have been spent either on reading or watching things. I really should just sit down and program for 5 minutes instead of watching random youtube clips. Next weeking is the global game jam, so I will atleast do some game things then :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 03</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 21:16:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There weren&amp;rsquo;t lot of dev time this week either. I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking at the bytecode and a basic assembler and disassembler for it. I&amp;rsquo;ve also commited a few rouge files found in the euphoria repo, but nothing major.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 02</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 22:00:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-02/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I been mostly handling real-world stuff and only manage to a little bit of work on euphoria, mainly fixing the travis build. Better luck next week I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 23:04:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First week of the new year. I started replacing my cutom log with spdlog and updating paths from strings to a dir/file path struct and continued the work on parsing the synty assets that I bought during black friday. There is still some work before euphoria can load and render it correctly but it&amp;rsquo;s coming along&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 52</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-52/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 22:19:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-52/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the last devlog of the year and unfortunatley I haven&amp;rsquo;t done much on either euphoria or fel this week as I&amp;rsquo;ve spended most of it with friends and family. However I started replacing the custom log with spdlog so that is atleast something&amp;hellip; :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 51</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-51/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 21:45:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-51/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I added grid snapping, simple object movement and selection to t3d.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 50</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 22:24:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-50/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I continued the work on t3d and can now place items on a grid. Hopefully next week I can get back to working on fel for a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 49</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-49/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 23:38:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-49/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I forgot my plan and bought some 3d assets on a black-friday sale so I&amp;rsquo;ve spent most, if not all, of my time integrating my level editor t3d into euphoria and trying to make it usable. I&amp;rsquo;ve fixed so that it loads the tile meshes and I&amp;rsquo;m currently adding collision detecion so I can add selection and interaction. Until next time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 48</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 23:27:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-48/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I started working on bytecode and a vm for fel and I added a simple svg debug renderer to euphoria. Next week I really hope I can run bytecode in vm and compile fel code to bytecode.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 47</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-47/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 23:41:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-47/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I worked on fel. The basic parser and ast tree is now working, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to implement the bytecode generation and vm.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 46</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 23:16:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-46/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I wrote AST generation for fel and then I went back to cleaning up the tree generation for euphoria hoping that I can quickly move it to fel for debugging purposes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
