<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gustav Janssons devlog </title>
    <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/</link>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;This blog is a try to me keep motivates and a way to see my progress on my current projects. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how it goes!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 23:40:32 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/devlog/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    
    
    

    
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 40</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-40/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 23:31:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-40/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I started working on basic profiler for tred, I picked up euphoria and started cleaning up the cmake setup and continued work on gaf so that it&amp;rsquo;s more streamlined faster testing and contains the features that I want in euphoria&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 39</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-39/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 22:46:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-39/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I fixed so that the euphoria tracery could handle extended json and added some more design notes for tred. I actually also started on a new project textgen where you generate textures by drawing graphs or writing lua code. Nothing to show yet but I only worked on it for 30 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 38</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 21:35:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-38/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I copied the script used to create the &amp;lsquo;game programming patterns&amp;rsquo; book and rewrote most of it to be generic instead of tied to a specific book. Apperently it didn&amp;rsquo;t support ebook generation so I&amp;rsquo;ll probably add that eventually. The rest of the week was spent on reading up on engine design and some refactoring of tred so no new major features.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 37</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 21:41:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-37/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I mostly spent watching netflix. Lazy I know but I atleast structure the todo list and think on how the tred api will be layed out&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 36</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 21:22:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-36/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I continued to work on the 3d rendering in tred. We got some basic lighting now :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 35</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 21:04:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-35/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I continued work on tred, almost got basic lighting done now.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 34</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 21:34:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-34/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Less heat this week. I continued on tred, added uniforms and attributes to the shader and I finally think I got a good design going. I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on getting uniform textures working fully. The plan is to work in tred for a month or two and then integrate it into euphoria. We&amp;rsquo;ll see how it goes&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 33</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 22:06:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-33/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I started working on tred, my temporary 3d engine. Nothing much got done since it&amp;rsquo;s currently superhot and I&amp;rsquo;m sitting behind a fan, and I&amp;rsquo;ve decided that for next year I&amp;rsquo;m getting myself an AC for the appartment cause this is unbearable. Until next time&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 32</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 22:09:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-32/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I didn&amp;rsquo;t do much, but after much consideration I moved all the euphoria source to a src folder so that the project root is a bit cleaner.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 31</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 19:51:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-31/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Theese past weeks I spent in the hospital and recovering from said experience. Nothing major was done really mostly config/dotfiles changes. Hopefully I will get back to euphoria I netflix will stop interfering :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 26</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 21:54:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-26/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I mostly watched netfix and such but I did manage to implement a simple fill tool for the pixel image editor.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 25</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 22:32:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I changed to my main computer, started transfering my old PrettyGood.net from google code to github, and finally started working on euphoria again. This time I started working on a custom pixel editing program. It&amp;rsquo;s far from finished but I hope that it can be useful in a few weeks time for the GMTK game jam.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 24</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 21:24:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I ported a old anagram application from c# to python, I published and updated old &amp;ldquo;engines&amp;rdquo;, one called hmtest and one called pwn-engine, so I could run them, but it turns out that none of them was that advanced. I also installed arch on my main, so either this week or the next my transition to arch will be complete&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 23</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:45:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I started refactoring bbcalc so it could in the future handle generating truth tables, and I physically moved things around so I now use arch as my main computer. It will probably be a week or two until I install it on my main machine, but not too long since this hardware isn&amp;rsquo;t really health&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 22</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 23:40:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2020-22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I completed my kodsnack gamejam, and started on porting one of my filemover programs from c#+winforms to python+curses&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
