<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gustav Janssons devlog </title>
    <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/</link>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;This blog is a try to me keep motivates and a way to see my progress on my current projects. Let&#39;s see how it goes!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 23:40:32 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/devlog/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    
    
    

    
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 52</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-52/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 22:19:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-52/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the last devlog of the year and unfortunatley I haven&#39;t done much on either euphoria or fel this week as I&#39;ve spended most of it with friends and family. However I started replacing the custom log with spdlog so that is atleast something&amp;hellip; :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 51</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-51/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 21:45:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-51/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I added grid snapping, simple object movement and selection to t3d.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 50</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 22:24:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-50/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I continued the work on t3d and can now place items on a grid. Hopefully next week I can get back to working on fel for a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 49</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-49/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 23:38:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-49/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I forgot my plan and bought some 3d assets on a black-friday sale so I&#39;ve spent most, if not all, of my time integrating my level editor t3d into euphoria and trying to make it usable. I&#39;ve fixed so that it loads the tile meshes and I&#39;m currently adding collision detecion so I can add selection and interaction. Until next time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 48</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 23:27:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-48/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I started working on bytecode and a vm for fel and I added a simple svg debug renderer to euphoria. Next week I really hope I can run bytecode in vm and compile fel code to bytecode.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 47</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-47/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 23:41:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-47/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I worked on fel. The basic parser and ast tree is now working, and it&#39;s time to implement the bytecode generation and vm.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 46</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 23:16:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-46/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I wrote AST generation for fel and then I went back to cleaning up the tree generation for euphoria hoping that I can quickly move it to fel for debugging purposes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 45</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-45/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 23:20:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-45/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I added basic cp437 functions to euph and refactored the current font to use the utf8 character encoding instead of some unspecified encoding that looked like ascii. I moved some part of the rendering to core and replaced the rendering text on image with the &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; core font instead of just the single built in font. With the increased intrest in text rendering/drawing with text and cp437 I looked into implementing part of the figlet specification, so that might happen. Finnaly I deceded to start pushing some fel code, even though it&#39;s not working. I&#39;m working on it and I still hope to have a fully working parser and vm before the start of december. I think that&#39;s about it for now.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 44</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-44/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 22:47:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-44/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I found a cool piece of code that can display a tree in the terminal, and since it was MIT licensed I&#39;ve been working on integrating it and making the API nice to use.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 43</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-43/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 20:56:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-43/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I picked up and slightly restarted my scriping language fel. A part of me want&#39;s to get it ready for december so I atleast can solve the first problems in it. Fingers crossed.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 42</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 21:54:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-42/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I fixed bugs introduced by moving musikmaskin to euphoria and refactored other parts of euphoria.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 41</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-41/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 23:02:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-41/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I continued my work on euphoria, fixing various style issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 40</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-40/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 23:54:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-40/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I added namespace and moved clang-format from the cmake build system to a python script&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 39</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-39/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 22:44:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-39/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I didn&#39;t do much. Only minor scrip editing and code writing&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 38</title>
      <link>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 23:11:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i.madeso.me/devlog/2019-38/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I finished the kodsnack gamejam. I also bought a nerf distruptor. Not really related to development but I bought it as a stress reliever and it&#39;s suprisingly fun to shoot at targets.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
