<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Year-in-Review on Gustav Jansson</title>
    <link>https://madeso.github.io/tags/year-in-review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Year-in-Review on Gustav Jansson</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 20:54:16 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://madeso.github.io/tags/year-in-review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2023 in review</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/2023-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 20:54:16 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/2023-in-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another year full of devlogs and another review of what I have achieved and failed to achieve.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;workbench-euphoria-gaf-and-json&#34;&gt;workbench, euphoria, gaf and json&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Workbench started out as a repo of various build scripts, but is now a single tool for running all those &amp;ldquo;scripts&amp;rdquo;. This year I ported everything from rust to c# and scoured my repos for other tools to integrate it into the code base.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the big reasons for choosing C# is so that I can use the spectre project to get a nicer cli.&#xA;The other big reason is that I use c# as a language for work so I&amp;rsquo;m very familiar with it. I can also use resharper to clean up the code and do major refactorings, that wasn&amp;rsquo;t really possible with the rust or the python version.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2022 in review</title>
      <link>https://madeso.github.io/blog/2022-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 17:19:08 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://madeso.github.io/blog/2022-in-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently realized that I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing my devlog since 2017 but I have never compiled all the devblogs into a longer post starting from today. I&amp;rsquo;ll summarize and write a smallish review of what I&amp;rsquo;ve done on all my hobby projects the past year.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;euphoria&#34;&gt;Euphoria&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Euphoria is my hobby game engine and to much surprise I did a couple of cool things related to it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Code wise I&amp;rsquo;ve continued to code cleanup (replacing streams with fmt), both warnings and enabled warning-as-errors(with w4/Wall+extra), I also added both a clang-tidy and coverage step on github actions so I can keep the code clean and strive towards a 100% coverage for the core. Added a PCH cut the compilation time by roughly 66%.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
